威尔 · 森特斯: 有人能提出一个更好的方法吗
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Can
anybody propose a better way
每个用户都有每个函数的副本更重要吗？
than having copies of each
function on every single user?
但是记住我还是想做这个。
But remembering I still
wanna be able to do this.
好吧，先等一下。
Well, hold on that thought for a moment.
有人能想出更好的办法吗？
Can someone think of a better way?
杰夫，你有一个苦笑，你想。
Jeff, you've got a wry smile on,
you wanna.
杰夫: 嗯，你可以用一个项目来创建一个原型。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Well, you could use
a project create a prototype.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，也许凯利，你会有一个直观上可以想到的想法
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes, maybe Kelly, you
will have a thought what intuitively could
而不是把我们所有的函数复制到每一个对象上？
we do rather than have copies of all our
functions one on every single object?
我们能做什么，只是在一个非常直接的感觉，托德？
What could we do, just in a very
straightforward sense, Todd?
托德: 嗯，我只是有一个主要用户，我们可以参考每个。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Well, I just have a main
user that we can reference each.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 很接近，非常，非常直观和简单，布雷顿？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Close, just very,
very intuitive and simple, Braydon?
让函数接受你正在使用的对象。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Make functions that
accept the object you're using.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这是另一种方式，但问题是,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That is another way,
but the problem with that then,
然后我们回到旧世界，我的功能在哪里？
then we fall back into the old
world of where's my function?
我可以把它应用到任何事情上。
I can apply it to anything.
所以，我们希望它们以同样的方式捆绑，是吗，马特？
So, we want them to be bundled
in the same way, yeah, Matt?
马特: 只要添加一个函数就行了。
&gt;&gt; Matt: Just add the one function.
只要在一个对象中添加一个函数
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Just add
the one function in an object and
不知何故，JavaScript 知道当它
somehow have JavaScript know that when it
在 user2上没有找到 increment，没有放弃。
doesn't find increment on user2,
not give up.
在 user2上没有增量函数。
Have us no increment function on user2.
在 user1上没有增量函数，但是
No increment function on user1, but
一个单一的物体，威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们
a single object,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We
可以称之为，我不知道，功能商店。
could call it, I don't know,
function store.
我们会使用一个函数，所以我不知道
We'll use a function, so I don't know, and
这里有我们的增量功能。
in there have our increment functionality.
并且希望 JavaScript 有一些特性
And somehow hope that
JavaScript has some feature
那就意味着当它找不到。
that will mean that when it does not find.
它转到 user2，寻找内存，寻找增量属性,
It goes user2, looks for the memory,
looks for the increment property on it,
不会发现，不会惊慌，不会放弃，但是不知怎么的，知道要去
doesn't find, doesn't panic, doesn't
give up, but somehow knows to go and
找到这个对象中的函数，抓取它的代码，并运行它。
find the function in this object,
grabs its code, and runs it.
这正是 JavaScript 要做的。
And that's exactly what
JavaScript's gonna do.
原型链，我们将增量函数存储在一个对象中。
The prototype chain, we're gonna store
the increment function in just one object.
然后让 JavaScript 解释它。
And have the JavaScript interpret it.
这就是看着它的部分，然后问我该怎么处理它？
That's the bit that looks at it and
goes what do I do with that?
这个词是什么意思？
What's this word mean?
我去找那个。
While I go look for that.
如果没有在 user1上找到函数，或者在本例中没有在 user2上找到函数,
Have it, if it doesn't find the function
on user1, or in this case user2,
不是放弃，而是以某种方式查找对象，找到 increment 并使用它。
not give up, but somehow look up to
that object, find increment, and use it.
我们必须链接 user1或 user2，以及我创建的函数存储对象。
We've gotta link user1 or user2, and this
function store object that I've created.
所以解释器，我们没有发现增量,
So the interpreter,
we're not finding increment,
一定要检查功能商店，它会找到它。
makes sure to check up to function store,
where it would find it.
正如 Jeff 所暗示的那样，使用 object.create 技术创建链接。
And exactly as Jeff hinted, make that
link using the object.create technique.
这里是人们。
Here it is people.
看看，用户创建的函数是如何改变的，我们还在创建我们的新用户。
Have a look, how user created functions
change, we're still making our new user.
但现在我们使用对象 create 技术来创建对象,
But now we're using the object.create
technique to create the object,
看看这个。
and look at this.
它仍然是一个空物体。
It's still gonna be an empty object.
但是我有一种感觉，事实上我们正在通过用户功能存储,
But I have a feeling that the fact that
we're passing in user function store,
我们称之为用户函数存储,
we're gonna call it user function store,
看起来是一个更大的有两个函数的物体。
which is by the looks of it a bigger
object here with two functions.
我添加了另外一个，增量和登录。
I've added another one,
increment and login.
我在这个物体的幕后有一个链接。
And I'm somehow gonna have a link
behind the scenes on this object.
不会有递增函数。
There's gonna be no increment function.
上面不会有递增函数。
There's gonna be no
increment function on it.
有人看到我给新的用户对象添加了一个增量函数吗？
Anybody see me adding an increment
function to new user object?
我没看到。
I don't see one.
但不知怎么的，它会有一个链接到共享存储功能。
But somehow it is gonna have a link
to the shared storage functions.
也就是说当我们把物体放回去时,
Meaning when we return the object out,
那个链接仍然是共享的存储功能。
that link is gonna still be
that shared store functions.
威尔 · 森特斯: 这将会非常非常好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's gonna be very,
very nice.
顺便说一句,
By the way,
这种方法可以从根本上实现我们想要的一切。
this approach here is gonna fundamentally
achieve all the things we wanna achieve.
除了需要写一些代码之外。
Besides the fact that it's gonna
involve a bit of writing a code.
也许有一些简单的方法可以达到这个目的。
And there might be some shorthand
ways of achieving this.
解决方案三
And solution three and
四个只会缩短做这件事的时间。
four are just gonna be shortened
ways of doing just this thing.
这是绝对的核心。
This is the absolute core.